certifiedpsychics.com 2016-02-08

# Psychic Readings - Our Privacy Policy

| 

The American Associaiton of Professional Psychics, Inc. knows you are concerned about your privacy. We take the issue of Internet Privacy very seriously. By using using our site and/or our services, you consent to the use and disclosure of the personal imformation you provide to us as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Please see Terms of Use for additional information. 

If you have any questons or concerns, email us at customerservice@certifiedpsychics.com.

| 

|  | 

What security do you provide?
What information do you collect?
What about credit cards?
Do you sell personal information?
Does anyone else have access to my information?
What about my IP Address?
What about children? 
What about the phone numbers on your site?
|  |    

What security do you provide?  

    We take every precaution to protect our users’ information. We use the industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption and firewalls to protect against loss, misuse, and alteration of any personal data under our control. While on a secure page such as our Secure Order Forms, there is a “locked” icon on the bottom of Web browsers.
 
What information do you collect? 
    We collect the information you give us when you fill out a form on our site.  

What about credit cards?   

    Your credit card information is never stored by our site. 
    When you use a credit card from our site, the information is sent by SSL and processed by a Merchant Bank. We do not see nor do we store your credit card information.
 
Do you sell personal information to third parties? 
    We do no sell or otherwise distribute any personal information to third parties. Not ever. 
 
Does anyone else have access to my personal information?
     
    No.

What about my IP address?  

    For your protection, when anyone makes a credit card transaction from our site, we log the IP address.   

What about children?
    Our services are not intened for use by individuals under the age of 18. If you are not at least 18 years of age, do not attempt to contact our psychics.
 
What about the phone numbers on your site?  

    When you call a phone number shown on our site, your phone call is not linked to any information that may have been collected on the web site. The call-in program is completely separate from the web site. Your phone call is private, between you and your psychic. You phone call information, such as the number from which you are calling, is tracked by the phone companies like other phone calls.

|
